At browserlock.net, accessible from [https://browserlock.net](https://browserlock.net/), one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by browserlock.net and how we use it.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website/web extension product with regards to the information that they shared and/or is collected in Browser Lock web application product.

Consent
-------

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

What information do we collect
------------------------------

The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

### Personally Identifiable Information:

In this product, we ask your affirmative consent to collect your **email address** to facilitate the creation of your personal account on Browser Lock. In the user experience flow, we also ask you to create your own **password** in order to log into your newly created personal account. Please use a new password that is different from your other personal accounts to protect your data security in case of data breach on other platforms.

In addition to your email address and password, we also collect the information transmitted in the standard HTTP header, such as your **IP address, device type, and browser type**.

If you contact us directly via the contact email, we may receive additional information about you, such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.

### Product Usage Information:

When you use our product and service, we also collect basic usage information, including: page loaded in the product, settings opened action, and your click actions on the quicklinks.

We do not collect the full URL behind each quicklinks that you click on. We only save the general domain (such as facebook.com) for statistical purposes.

How do we collect your information
----------------------------------

Log Files
---------

[browserlock.net](https://browserlock.net/) follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

Cookies and Web Beacons
-----------------------

Like any other website, [browserlock.net](https://browserlock.net/) uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.

For more general information on cookies, please read ["What Are Cookies" from Cookie Consent](https://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies/).

How do we use your information
------------------------------

We use the information we collect about you in various ways, including:

* Provide, operate, and maintain our product/website/service
* Improve and expand our product/website/service
* Understand and analyze how users interact our product/website/service
* Develop new products, services, features, and functionality
* Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes
* Find and prevent fraud

With whom do we share your information
--------------------------------------

### Our Advertising Partners

While using our product, you will see sponsored advertisements in the format of affiliate links. These advertisements are displayed based on your geographic region. All the users from the same geographic region (country) will see the same sponsored ads/affiliate links. They are not customized based on your preference, online behaviors, browsing history, or usage of the product. In the process of showing you these sponsored ads in the format of affiliate links, we do not share your personal information with the advertising partners.

However, once you click on the affiliate links, leave our product, and proceed to the landing pages or destination sites of these third-party advertising vendors, our Privacy Policy will no longer cover your usage and interaction with their product/service. Please check their Privacy Policy and make your decisions accordingly.

### Our Analytics Partners

Mixpanel and Yandex are our analytics system providers.

### Our Service Providers

Google Firebase Realtime Database is where your user data is stored.

Third Party Privacy Policies
----------------------------

[browserlock.net](https://browserlock.net/)'s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

How do we protect your information
----------------------------------

We maintain tight controls over all the data we collect, retaining it in secured databases with limited and controlled access rights. Please remember that unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure, so although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted via the product; any transmission is at your own risk.

How long do we keep your information
------------------------------------

We keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary. Once you decide to uninstall/remove our product and stop using our website, we will keep your information for an additional six months before deleting them from our database.

Notice to EU Residents under the ”GDPR”)
----------------------------------------

This section applies to you if you are a national of a European Economic Area (“EEA”) member state. This section describes our good faith effort to meet our obligations under the GDPR.

### Personal Data

The GDPR, defines “personal data” as “…any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (‘data subject’); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person”

For the purposes of our Privacy Policy, the “data subject” is “you” (“your”, “user”). The personal data we collect may include: the unique User ID we assign you.

The personal data we collect will only be used and disclosed for the purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy.

Our basis for processing personal data: GDPR Article 6.1(a): “the data subject has given consent to the processing of his or her personal data for one or more specific purposes”; GDPR Article 6.1(b): “processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party or in order to take steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract”; GDPR Article 6(1)(f): “processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the controller or by a third party…”

### Your Rights

Your rights as a GDPR data subject, includes the following:

* Request a copy of information, if any, stored about you.
* Correct information, if any, stored about you.
* Erase information, if any, stored about you.
* Restrict how information, if any, about you is used.
* Transfer the information, if any, about you.
* Object to how your information, if any, is used in certain cases.
* Request why we are unable to fulfill your request, if applicable.

You can contact us to submit any GDPR related inquiry or request by submitting an inquiry to [\[email protected\]](https://browserlock.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Notice to California Residents under the ”CCPA”
-----------------------------------------------

This Section applies to you if you are a natural person who is a California resident, as defined in the California Code of Regulations. This section describes our good faith effort to meet our obligations under the CCPA.

### Personal Information

The CCPA, defines “personal information” as including “…information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.”

For the purposes of our Privacy Policy, the “person” is “you” (“your”, “user”). The personal information we may collect includes: IP Address; the unique User ID we assign you; the User Agent and version of your web browser; and the Operating System and version used by your hardware.

The personal information we collect will only be used and disclosed for the business purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy, which are necessary for us in order to provide you with the Service.

Your Rights / Opt-Out for “Sale of Personal Information”

You can contact us to submit any CCPA related inquiry or request via the following 2 methods:

Submitting an inquiry to [\[email protected\]](https://browserlock.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Sending a physical inquiry to 38 habrzal St., Tel Aviv, Israel

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights.

Children's Information
----------------------

This product is not designed for or targeting children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

[browserlock.net](https://browserlock.net/) does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our product/website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

Updates to Privacy Policy
-------------------------

This Privacy Policy will be updated from time to time. We strongly recommend you to check back here periodically to see if the Privacy Policy has been updated. We will always show the date of the latest modification of the Privacy Policy at the top of the page so you can tell when it was last revised.

Contact Us
----------

We regularly review our compliance with this Privacy Policy. Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [\[email protected\]](https://browserlock.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
